shape5.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy

Shape 5 LLC respects the privacy of its users whether they use our website located at www.shape5.com to purchase licenses to website templates, extensions, and other related software, utilize related services offered from time to time, or simply view the website. The following privacy policy is designed to inform you, as a user of this website, about the types of information that we may gather or collect from you in connection with your use of our website. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Shape5 LLC uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Each time you use our website, the current version of this privacy policy will apply. 

**BY USING OR ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

**Children**   
The Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Shape5 LLC does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**   
At the time of registration a user will need to submit the following information: full name, email address, a valid password, registration date, last visit date, purchase history, and IP address. Shape5 LLC is not involved in any way of the collection of this data, it is submitted solely by the user. No other information is required or collected at the time of registration or any at any other time or process of our website. This information is used to personalize a user's experience on our website and for occasional communication. This information is stored on an encrypted web server, and is not shared with any outside party with the exception of email addresses for newsletter correspondence (see Shared Information). This information is used to enable us to provide service to our customers, and maintain the security of their accounts. 

**Shared Information**   
Shape5 LLC does not share any user related information with any third party companies except for email addresses which are used solely for newsletter correspondence, which the user agrees to at the time of registration. Email addresses will be imported/exported using constantcontact.com, a mass emailing website, to use as acommunication tool with our members. 

**Financial Information**   
Any financial information such as credit card numbers are kept with our third-party payment processors: 2checkout and PayPal. Shape5 LLC does not store or request any financial information for any reason. 

**Support Communications**   
The support staff of Shape5 LLC may from time to time request access to a member's website to assist in debugging a product within their specified hosting environment or to make necessary modifications for the user. This may be done via email or through our support forums. Requests may include admin logins, ftp access, cpanel access, or general logins pertaining to the problem at hand. Only moderators of Shape5 LLC are authorized to ask for such information, the moderators of Shape5 LLC are: mikek, jonahh, mnicoll, and trineer. Any information requested by moderators is kept secure and confidential between just the moderator and the member themselves. Requested information is never shared with anyone but the moderator. 

**General Company Communications**   
All communication with Shape5 LLC and its customers is done via our website forum or via email. Phone support is not offered. 

**Security**   
We take security of your information, such as name and email address, very seriously and use reasonable electronic, personnel, and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration, or misuse. We work to protect your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you provide online at our Web Site

**Google Analytics**   
We do utilize Google Analytics on our website, as part of doing business. We use information gathered by Google Analytics to better understand our customers' needs and to detect any issues users are having with our websites. 

**Right of Removal**   
If you would like to request to have your personal information removed from our servers, you may do so by submitting a request via our [Contact Page](https://www.shape5.com/contact-us/contact_shape_5.html). All requests will be addressed within the time frame required under GDPR policies. Keep in mind that removing your data is permanent and will result in the cancellation of any currently-active services without refund, as well as any Member Bonuses. 

**Web Cookies**   
A Web Cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the site. Shape5 LLC's website will store cookies on user's machines to track membership durations, active logins and forum access. No personal information is recorded or collected at this time, it is simply used for normal membership processes of the website.

**Terms of Use**   
Please also take the time to review our Terms of Use page found [here](http://www.shape5.com/terms_of_use.html).
